Guide to the Samuel P. Hays Post-World War II Radical Movements Publications Collection, 1915-1982 AIS.1981.18
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Radical Left Publications, 1949-1982; IV.
  - Liberator (New York, NY: Liberation Committee for Africa), v. 1, May, July-Aug., Oct., 1961; v. 2, Jan., March, July-Aug., Nov.-Dec. 1962; v. 3, 1963/1964; v. 5-8, 1965-1968; v. 9, June-March 1969, 14.
  - Liberty House News (Jackson, MS: Liberty House), Nov.-Dec. 1971, 15.
  - Literature and Ideology (Montreal, Que.), no. 2-4, Summer-Winter 1969, 16.
  - Liberation (New York, NY), v. 8 no. 12, Feb. 1964; v. 9 no. 1-9, March-Dec. 1964; v. 10, 1965/1966; v. 11, April, Sept. 1966; v. 12-19, 1967/1968-1975/1976; v. 20 no. 1-6, Fall 1976-Fall 1977, 1. (Box 95)
  - Liberation News Service (New York, NY: New Media Project), no. 87-245, July 5, 1968-April 1970, 1. (Box 96)
  - Logos (Montreal, Que.), v. 1 no. 8-11, 1969; v. 2 no. 1-3, 1970; v. 3 no. 1-3, 5, 1971, 1. (Box 97)
  - London Bulletin (London, England: Russell Peace Foundation), no. 1-3, Aug.-Oct. 1967, 2.
  - Long March (Baltimore, MD), May 1965; Nov. 1965, Jan.1966; Spring-Summer 1966; Fall/Winter 1966/1967, 3.
  - M-CUP News (Minneapolis, MN), v. 1 no. 8-9, Sept.-Nov. 1967, 4.
  - MDS Newsletter (New Orleans, LA: New Orleans Movement for a Democratic Society), v. 2 no. 11-12, Nov.-Dec. 1968; v. 3 no. 1-2, Jan.-Feb. 1969, 5.
  - Magical Sceptre (McKees Rocks, PA), 1 issue, undated, 6.
  - Mainstream (New York, NY), v. 9 no. 9-12, Sept.-Dec., 1956; v. 10 no. 1-10, Jan.-Oct., 1957; v. 11-16 no. 8, 1958-Aug. 1963, 7.
  - Majority Report (Bloomington, IN), v. 1 no. 3, Nov. 1969, 8.
  - Malcriado, The Voice of the Farm Worker (Delano, CA), v. 2 no. 12-24, Nov. 1968-Feb. 1969; v. 3 no. 1-18, 20-21, March 1, 1969-Jan. 1970; Feb. 16/28-March 1/15, 1970, 9.
  - Marxist (London, England), no. 10-17, April 1969-Feb. 1971, 10.
  - Marxist-Leninist Vanguard (New York, NY), v. 9 no. 8-12, Aug.-Dec. 1967; v. 10, 1968; v. 11 no. 1-3, Jan.-March 1969, 11.
  - Manas (Los Angeles, CA), v. 6 no. 23-25, 28-29, 31, 33, 35-36, June 10-24, July 15-22, Aug. 5-10, Sept. 2-9, 1953; v. 7 no. 4, 10-46, Jan. 27, March 10-Nov. 17, 19, 1954; v. 9-19 no. 35, 1956-Aug. 31, 1966, 1. (Box 98)
  - Masses and Mainstream (New York, NY), v. 2 no. 7, July 1949; v. 6, 1953; v. 7, 1954 (lacks no. 4); v. 8, 1955; v. 9, no. 1, 3-8, Jan., March-Aug. 1956, 1. (Box 99)
  - Mayday (Washington, DC), no. 4, 7-21, Nov. 1, Nov. 22, 1968-March 10, 1969, 2.
  - McCarthy Advance (Washington, DC: McCarthy for President National Headquarters), v. 1 no. 1, 2, 4, May 9, May 23, July 4, 1968, 3.
  - Memo (Washington, DC: Women Strike for Peace). v. 5 no. 10, June/July 1967, 4.
  - Middle Earth (Iowa City, IA), v. 1 no. 18, undated, ca. May 1968; v. 2 no. 1, undated, ca. June 1968, 5.
  - Midnight Special (New Orleans, LA: New Orleans Movement for a Democratic Society), v. 1 no. 1-12, June 1970-Aug. 1971, 6.
  - Midpeninsula Observer (Palo Alto, CA), v. 1 no. 21, June 3-17, 1968; v. 2 no. 2-14, July 15-Dec. 19, 1968, 7.
  - Militant (New York, NY), v. 28-33, 1964-1969, 8.
  - Militant (New York, NY), v. 34 no.1-44, Jan.-Nov. 27, 1970, 1. (Box 100)
  - Mind Fucke (Washington, DC), no. 4, Fall 1968, 2.
  - Miner's Voice (Charleston, WV), v. 2 no. 7, Dec. 1971, 3.
  - Minor's Lamp (Boyertown, PA), no. 1, 2, 4, 5, undated, ca. 1969, 4.
  - Minority of One (Passaic, NJ), v. 9 no. 7-9, July-Sept. 1967; v. 10 no. 7-11, July-Nov. 1968, 5.
  - Mississippi Freelance (Greenville, MS), v. 1 no. 1-12, April 1969-March 1970, 6.
  - Mobilizer to End the War in Vietnam (New York, NY: The National Mobilization Committee), v. 1 no. 2-4, Feb. 6-April 15, 1967; v. 2 no. 1-2, Sept.1-Sept. 26, 1967; v. 3 no. 1, undated; v. 4 no. 1, Aug. 15, 1968; v. 5 no. 1, Oct. 25, 1968, 7.
  - Modern Utopian: The Magazine of Social Change (Medford, MA; Berkeley, CA), v. 1-4 no. 3/4, 1967-Summer/Fall 1970, 8.
  - MoJo: Organ of Black Student Congress (New York, NY), v. 1 no. 5-7, 11-12, June-Aug., Dec. 1968, 9.
  - Moravian (Bethlehem, PA: Moravian Church in America, Northern Province), v. 111 no. 2-12, Feb.-Dec. 1966; v. 112-115 no. 2, 1967-Feb. 1970, 10.
  - Mount Royal Bulletin = Bulletin de Mont Royal ( Montreal, Que.: New Democratic Party = Nouveau Partie Democratique), v. 1 no. 1-2, Nov-Dec. 1963, 11.
  - Movement (San Francisco, CA: Movement Press), v. 3 no. 6-12, June-Dec. 1967; v. 4-5, 1968-1969; v. 6 no. 1, Feb./March 1970, 12.
  - Monthly Review (New York, NY), v. 4 no. 10-12, Feb.-April 1953; v. 5-17, 1953/1954-1965/1966; v. 18 no. 1-7, May-Dec. 1966; v. 21 no. 6-11, Nov. 1969-April 1970; v. 22 no. 1-6, May 1970-Nov. 1970, 1. (Box 101)
  - NACLA Newsletter (New York, NY: North American Congress on Latin America), v. 1 no. 3-10, April 1967-Jan. 1968; v. 2 no. 1-10, March 1968-Feb. 1969; v. 3, March 1969-Feb. 1970; v. 4 no. 1-5, 9-10, March-Sept. 1970, Jan.-Feb. 1971; v. 5, no. 1-8, March-Dec. 1971, 1. (Box 102)
  - NUC Newsletter (Chicago, IL: New University Conference), v. 1 no. 1-4, 1968; v. 2 no. 1-3, Jan.-May 1969; v. 3 no. 1, 3, Aug., Sept. 1969, 2.
  - Portland Eagle (Portland, OR), v. 1, no. 1, April 18, 1967, 3.
  - National Eagle (Portland, OR), v. 5, no. 1, 3-4, Aug. 15, Oct. 27-Nov. 27, 1966, 4.
  - National Underground Review (New York, NY), v. 1 no. 5, Aug. 1968, 5.
  - National Voter (Washington, DC: League of Women Voters of the United States), v. 13, no. 4, Aug. 1963, 6.
  - Negotiate Now! Bulletin (New York, NY), v. 1 no. 2, July 4, 1967, 7.
  - Negro Traveler and Conventioneer (Chicago, IL: Travelers Research Pub. Co.), v. 14 no. 7/8-9/10, July/Aug.-Sept./Oct., 1968; v. 15 no. 1, 10/11, March, Oct./Nov. 1969, 8.
  - New America (New York, NY: Socialist Party), v. 6 no. 4-5, 9-15, 19, Nov. 18-30, 1966; Feb. 16- May 31, Aug 22, 1967; v. 7 no. 2-22, Oct. 31, 1967-Nov. 30, 1968; v. 8 no. 1-12, 14-19, 23, Dec. 19, 1968-June 30, 1969, Aug. 31-Nov. 24, 1969, Jan. 31, 1970; v. 9 no. 2-10, 12-22, Feb. 25-June 30, 1970, Sept. 15, 1970-Feb. 28, 1971; v. 10 no. 1-3, 5-18, 20-22, April 20-May 15, 1971, July 30, 1971-July 31, 1972, Sept. 30-Nov. 15, 1972; v. 11 no. 1-4, 6-22, Dec. 31, 1972-March 20, 1973, April 25, 1973-March 28, 1974; v. 12 no. 1-4, April 30-July 20, 1974, 9.
  - New Babylon Times (Battleboro, VT), no. 1, Fall 1969, 10.
  - Green Mountain Post (Battleboro, VT), no. 2-4, Spring 1970-Summer 1972, 11.
  - New Call (Cedar Crest, NM), v. 1 no. 1-4, May-Dec. 1967, 12.
  - New Call Newsletter (Albuquerque, NM), v. 1 no. 1-8, Jan.-Aug. 1968, 13.
  - New Democratic Newsletter (Ottawa, Ont.), v. 1 no. 2-6, Dec. 1963-May 1964, 14.
  - New England Free Press (Boston, MA: New England Students for a Democratic Society), v. 1 no. 1-2, Sept. 26-Oct. 12, 1967; 1 issue, undated, ca. 1967, 15.
  - New Foundation (Lawrence, KS), v. 2 no. 1, Jan./Feb. 1970, 16.
  - New Left Notes (Chicago, IL: Students for a Democratic Society), v. 2 no. 22, 24-35, 37-45, June 5, June 9-Oct. 9, Oct. 23-Dec. 25, 1967; v. 3 no. 1-40, Jan.8,1968-Jan. 9, 1969; v. 4 no. 2-16, 25-32, Jan. 15-April 24, July 24-Oct. 21, 1969, 17.
  - New Left Notes (Boston, MA: Students for a Democratic Society), v. 5, no. 1-2, 4, June 30-July 30, Sept. 20, 1969, 18.
  - New Left Review (London, England), no. 54-65, March 1, 1969-Feb. 1, 1971, 19.
  - National Guardian: The Progressive Newsweekly (New York, NY), v. 4 no. 24, 48-52, April 2, Sept. 18-Oct. 16, 1952; v. 5-23 no. 14, Oct. 23, 1952-Jan. 2, 1971, 1. (Box 103, Box 104, Box 105, Box 106)
  - New World Review (New York, NY), v. 21 no. 2-10, Feb.-Dec. 1953; v. 22-32, 1954-1964; v. 33, no. 1-2, 4, Jan.-Feb., April 1965; v. 35 no. 7-9, July-Fall 1967; v. 36-38, 1968-1970, 1. (Box 107)
  - New Mobilizer (Washington, DC: New Mobilization Committee to End the War in Vietnam), no. 1, Sept. 5, 1969; no. 3, undated; no. 13-32, 34-51, Sept. 11, 1967-Feb. 21, 1968, March 6-Sept. 1/14, 1968, 1. (Box 108)
  - New Politics: A Journal of Socialist Thought (New York, NY), v. 1-3, 1961/1962-1963/1964; v. 4, no. 1-3, Winter-Summer 1965, 2.
  - New Politics News (New York, NY: National Conference for New Politics), v. 1 no. 3-5, Aug.-Nov., 1967; Convention issue no. 1, 1968, 3.
  - New Rank and Filer (Detroit, MI: Independent Workers Coordinating Committee), v. 1 no. 1-2, Feb.-March 1968, 4.
  - New Schools Exchange Newsletter (Santa Barbara, CA: New Schools Exchange), no. 29, 1970; no. 53-54, 57-70, 1971-1972, 5.
  - New Solidarity (New York, NY), May 18, 1970, 6.
  - New South Student (Nashville, TN), v. 2 no. 6, Nov. 1965; v. 3 no. 7, Nov. 1966; v. 4-5, 1967-1968; v. 6 no. 1, Jan. 1969, 7.
  - New Times (Moscow, USSR), no. 15, April 16, 1969, 8.
  - New West Magazine (Santa Monica, CA), no. 1-3, Nov. 1966-1967, 9.
  - New Worker (Los Angeles, CA), v. 1 no. 1-2, 5, 7, June-July, Oct., Dec.1969, 10.
  - New York High School Free Press (New York, NY), no. 3-8, Nov. 20/Dec. 11, 1968-April/May, 1971, 11.
  - News and Letters (Detroit, MI), v. 11 no. 7-9, Oct.-Dec. 1966; v. 12, 1967; v. 13, 1968 (lacks Feb.); v. 14-17, 1969-1972; v. 18 no. 1-4, Jan.-April 1973, 12.
  - News From McCarthy for President (Washington, DC), v. 1 no. 1, Jan. 25, 1968, 13.
  - News From William Penn House (Washington, DC), 2 issues, undated, 14.
  - News Notes of the Central Committee for Conscientious Objectors (Philadelphia, PA), v. 18 no. 4, July/Aug. 1966; v. 19 no. 2-6, March-Dec. 1967; v. 20-21, 1968-1969; v. 22 no. 1, 1st quarter 1970, 15.
  - Newsfront International (Oakland, CA: Peoples Translation Service), no. 237-241, June-Nov. 1980, 16.
  - Newsletter (London, England: Central Committee of the Socialist Labour League), v. 11 no. 514-529, Oct. 21, 1967-Feb. 10, 1968; v. 13 no. 668, July 5, 1969, 17.
  - Newsletter of the Philadelphia Anti Draft Union (Philadelphia, PA), 3 issues, undated, ca. Nov.- Dec., 1967, Jan. 1968, 18.
  - Newsletter of the Universities Committee on the Problems of War and Peace (Detroit, MI), March, June 1964, 19.
  - Northern Informer (Belfast, Northern Ireland), no. 9, July 5, 1969, 20.
  - Ocean Freedom (Santa Monica, CA), v. 1 no. 1-3, March 31-July, 1967, 1. (Box 109)
  - Ocean Living (Santa Monica, CA), v. no. 4-7, 9-10, undated, 2.
  - Ohio Valley Region Mobilizer to End the War in Vietnam (Cleveland, OH), v. 1 no. 2, April 28, 1967, 3.
  - Operation Freedom (Cincinnati, OH), Nov. 1967, 4.
  - Other Scenes (Greenwich Village, New York, NY), v. 3 no. 10, Aug. 1/14, 1969, 5.
  - P. L. Boston News (Cambridge, MA: Boston Progressive Labor Party), Spring, 1968, 6.
  - PL, Progressive Labor (Brooklyn, NY: Progressive Labor Party), v. 5 no. 5-6, Oct./Nov. 1966-Feb./March 1967; v. 6 no. 1-6, July/Aug. 1967-Feb. 1969; v. 7 no. 1, May 1969, 7.
  - Pacific Research and World Empire Telegram (East Palo Alto, CA: Pacific Studies Center), v. 1 no. 1-2, Aug. 3-Sept. 10, 1969, 8.
  - Pacific Sun (San Rafael, CA), Year 8 no. 34, 36, July 15, July 29, 1970, 9.
  - Papel (Albuquerque, NM: United Mexican American Students), March 1969, 10.
  - Paper (East Lansing, MI: Students of Michigan State University), v. 2 no. 27, Summer 1967, 11.
  - Paper Tiger (Boston, MA), v. 1 no. 2-7, Nov. 20, 1967-June 1968, 12.
  - Partisan: Magazine of Youth Against War and Fascism (New York, NY), v. 3, Spring-Fall, 1967; v. 4, Winter-Summer, 1968; v. 5, 1 issue undated and April 1969, 13.
  - Peace and Freedom News (Berkeley, CA: Peace and Freedom Movement of Alameda County), v. 1 no. 10-14, July 8-Sept. 16, 1968, 14.
  - Peace and Freedom News (Madison, WI: National Coordinating Committee to End the War in Vietnam), no. 34, Nov. 18, 1966, 15.
  - Peacemaker (Cincinnati, OH: Peacemaker Movement), v. 20 no. 8-17, June 3-Dec. 30, 1967; v. 21-22, 1968-1969; v. 23, no. 1-11, Jan. 17-Sept. 12, 1970; v. 24 no. 5, 6, 8, 10, April 10, May 1, June 12, Aug. 14, 1971, 16.
  - Peace News (London, England), no. 1389, 1418-1515, Feb. 8, Aug. 30, 1963-July 9, 1965, 17.
  - People Soup (Boston, MA), v. 6 no. 1, Oct. 1978, 18.
  - People's Voice (Bellflower, CA: Communist Party of the U.S.A.), v. 4 no. 1-3, July-Oct. 1968; v. 5 no. 1-2, June-Sept., 1970, 19.
  - People's Voice (Los Angeles, CA), v. 1 no. 1-13, Aug. 23-Dec. 27, 1965; v. 2 no. 1-23, Feb. 21-Dec. 19, 1966; v. 3 no. 1-27, Jan. 2-Dec. 25, 1967, 20.
  - Peoples Yellow Pages (Cleveland, OH; Cambridge, MA: Vocations for Social Change), 2 issues, undated, 21.
  - Petal Paper (Montgomery, AL), v. 12, no. 9, 12, July, Oct. 1965; v. 13 no. 4-7, Feb.-May 1966, 22.
  - Philadelphia Anti-Draft Union Newsletter (Philadelphia, PA), 3 issues, undated, 23.
  - Phoenix (Nashville, TN: Southern Student Organizing Committee), v. 1 no. 1-6, Aug. 1968-March 1969, 24.
  - Pine Tree (Santa Ana, CA), Spring 1970, 25.
  - Pittsburgh Draft Resistance (Pittsburgh, PA), 1 issue, undated, 26.
  - Pittsburgh Human Relations Review (Pittsburgh, PA), v. 12 no. 4, Winter 1969; v. 13, no. 2-5, Summer; 1970-Spring/Summer/Fall 1971, 27.
  - Pittsburgh Peace and Freedom News (Pittsburgh, PA: Pittsburgh Committee to End the War in Vietnam), v. 1 no. 3-5, 7, 9-10, Sept.-Nov. 1966, March, May-June, 1967; v. 2 no. 2-6, 8, 10, Sept. 1967-March 1968, May/June 1968, Feb. 1969; v. 3 no. 1, Sept. 1969; v. 4 no. 1-3, Jan.-July 1970; Special issue, June 22, 1971;v. 5 no. 2, Feb. 1972, 28.
  - Plain Rapper (Palo Alto, CA: Palo Alto Resistance), v. 1 no. 1-7, Jan. 10-Nov. 1969, 29.
  - Plain Truth: Serving the North End (Champaign, IL), no. 13, 15-16, 18-19, Sept. 1968, Dec. 1968-Jan. 1969, March-April 1969, 30.
  - People's World (San Francisco, CA), v. 30 no. 22-52, June 3-Dec. 30, 1967; v. 31-32, 1968-1969; v. 33 no. 1-16, 18-42, 47-48, 1970, 1. (Box 110)
  - Political Affairs (New York, NY), Oct.-Dec. 1967; 1968-1970, 1. (Box 111)
  - Portuguese and Colonial Bulletin (London, England), v. 9 no. 2-4, July 1969-Jan. 1970; v. 10 no. 1-3, April-Oct. 1970, 2.
  - Power Line (Washington, DC: Environmental Action Foundation), v. 1 no. 1-11, July 1975-May 1976; v. 2 no. 3-5, 7-12, Oct. 1976-June 1977; v. 3 no. 1-2, 8-11, July-Aug. 1977, Feb.-June 1978; v. 4 no. 1, 3-12, July 1978, Sept. 1978-July 1979; v. 5 no. 1-11, Aug. 1979-June 1980, 3.
  - Preform Inform (Santa Monica, CA), no. 1-8, June 1968-March 1970, 4.
  - Prevent World War III (New York, NY: Society for the Prevention of World War III), no. 70-75, Summer 1967-Winter/Spring 1970, 5.
  - Prism (Princeton, NJ), v. 1 no. 1-4, Oct. 14-Dec. 13, 1967, 6.
  - Progressive Labor: Bay Area Newsletter (San Francisco, CA: Progressive Labor Party), Feb.-March, June, 1968, 7.
  - Progressive People's Party (Chicago, IL), v. 1 no. 1-2, May-June 1969; Special issue, undated, 8.
  - Progressive Record (Cincinnati, OH), v. 3, no. 2, June 1966; v. 10 no. 10, Jan. 1967, 9.
  - Progressive Worker (Vancouver, B.C.), v. 4 no. 6, April 1968, 10.
  - Protos (Los Angeles, CA), v. 1 no. 2, Dec. 1969; v. 1 no. 5, March 1970; Special issue, 1970, 11.
  - Quaker Action Group Newsletter (Philadelphia, PA), no. 19, May/June 1969; no. 21-23, Sept. 1969-March 1970; no. 25, Nov. 1970; no. 27, May 1971, 12.
  - Quaker Service (Philadelphia, PA), Spring 1967, 13.
  - Radical America (Madison, WI: University of Wisconsin Students for a Democratic Society Free Press), v. 1 no. 2-3, Sept.-Dec. 1967; v. 2, 1968; v. 3, no. 1-5, Jan.-Sept. 1969, 14.
  - Radical America (Storrs, CT: Radical Education Project), v. 1 no. 1, April 1967; v. 3 no. 6, Nov. 1969, 15.
  - Radical Newspaper (New York, NY: SDS Labor Committee National Caucus), Dec. 1967, 16.
  - Radical Teacher (Chicago, IL),1 issue, undated, 17.
  - Radicals in the Professions Newsletter (Ann Arbor, MI: Radical Education Project), v. 1, no. 3-10, Jan.-Dec. 1968, 18.
  - Something Else (Ann Arbor, MI: Radical Education Project), v. 2, March 1969-March 1970; v. 3 no. 4, July 1971, 19.
  - Rap (Santa Ana, CA), Fall-Winter 1970, 20.
  - Raritan Peace News (New Brunswick, NJ), v. 1 no. 17-21, March 5-April 30, 1968, 21.
  - Raza (Los Angeles, CA: El Barrio Communications Project), v. 1 no. 11-16, March 31-Sept. 3 1968; v. 2 no. 1-11, Oct. 15, 1968-Feb. 1970, 22.
  - Raza Magazine (Los Angeles, CA: El Barrio Communications Project), v. 1 no. 1-3, undated, ca. March-June 1970, 23.
  - Realist (New York, NY: The Realist Association), no. 63-83, Oct. 1965-Oct. I968, 24.
  - Reason (Brighton, MA), v. 1 no. 3, Nov. 1969; v. 2 no. 2, 4-5, 7-12, Oct. 1969, Dec. 1969-Jan. 1970, March 1970-March 1971; v. 3 no. 1-3, April-June 1971, 25.
  - Reason: A Review of Politics (Fullerton, CA: California State College), v. 1 no. 1, 4, Mar, June/July, 1965; v. 2 no. 4, April/May 1966, 26.
  - Rebel Published in Exile (Montreal, Que.), v. 1 no. 1, March/April 1968, 27.
  - Rebellion News (Roxbury, MA), v. 1 no. 2-12, July 1967-May 1968; v. 2 no. 2-3, Oct.-Dec. 1968, 28.
  - Red Mole (London, England: Relgocrest), v. 1 no. 1-2, March 17-April 1, 1970, 29.
  - Regeneracion (Los Angeles, CA), v. 1 no. 1-10, Jan. 1970-Jan. 1971; v. 2 no. 1, Feb. 1971, 30.
  - Relative Truth (Pittsburgh, PA), v. 1 no. 2, Jan. 1970, 31.
  - Ramparts (San Francisco, CA), v. 6 no. 2-11, Sept. 1967-July 1968; v. 7-11, 1968/1969-1972/1973; v. 12 no. 1-5, July-Dec. 1973, 1. (Box 112)
  - Resist (Cambridge, MA), no. 2-48, Dec. 18, 1967-Dec. 2, 1970; no. 51-59, March 12, 1971-Feb. 22, 1972; no. 61-66, April 23, 1972-Oct. 6, 1972; no. 70-79, Feb. 28, 1973-Feb. 25, 1974; no. 81-89, May 20, 1974-Jan. 25, 1975; no. 91-113, March 31, 1975-March 31, 1977; no. 115-116, May/June-July/Aug. 1977; no. 120-135, Jan. 1978-Oct./Nov. 1980, 1. (Box 113)
  - Resist Memo (Madison, WI: Draft Resistance Clearing House), no. 2-4, May-July 1967, 2.
  - Resistance (San Francisco, CA: Citizens Committee for Nuclear Disarmament), no. 1, Dec. 1963, 3.
  - Resistance (Boston, MA), April-June, Sept.-Nov. 1968, 4.
  - Resistance Newsletter (Palo Alto, CA), no. 3, Oct. 1967, 5.
  - Revolutionary Age (Seattle, WA: Freedom Socialist Publications), v. 1 no. 1-3, 1968; v. 2 no. 1, 1970, 6.
  - Revolutionary Communist Youth Newsletter (New York, NY: Revolutionary Communist Youth), no. 9-10, Oct./Nov. 1971-Jan./Feb. 1972, 7.
  - Revolutionary Marxist Caucus Newsletter (New York, NY), no. 7-8, April-July, 1971, 8.
  - Revolutionary Youth Movement (Chicago, IL), 2 issues, undated, 9.
  - Rights and Reviews (New York, NY: New York Chapter of Congress on Racial Equality), Winter 1965; Autumn 1966; Winter, Summer 1968, 10.
  - Rights of Man (New Orleans, LA: Grow Project of the Southern Conference Educational Fund), v. 1 no. 1, 3-5, May-Nov. 1969, 11.
  - Ring Down (Detroit, MI), no. 58, Feb. 16, 1973, 12.
  - Ripsaw (New York, NY: Columbia University Graduate Student Union), v. 1 no. 1-2, Dec. 1968-Spring 1969, 13.
  - Roger Spark (Chicago, IL: Spark Publishing Co.), v. 1 no. 6-18, April-Nov. 1968; v. 2 no. 1-10, 1969?; v. 3 no. 1-9, 1970?, 14.
  - SNCC Newsletter (Atlanta, GA: Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee), v. 1 no. 4, June/July 1967, 15.
  - Sane World (Washington, DC), June-Aug. 1963; May 1967; Dec. 1971; March-April 1972, 16.
  - Sanity (London, England), May 1969, 17.
  - Sattva (Sarasota, FL), no. 1, Oct. 1, 1968, 18.
  - Satyrday (Toronto, Ont.), v. 3 no. 2-6, May-Sept. 1968, 19.
  - Scimitar (Ithaca, NY), no. 1-7, Aug.-Dec. 10, 1968, 20.
  - Sechaba (Dar Es Salaam, Tanzania), v. 3 no. 4, April 1969, 21.
  - Sevendays (New York, NY: Institute for New Communications), Preview ed. no. 1-10, March 3, 1975-July 26, 1976; v. 1 no. 1-10, Feb. 14-June 20, 1977; v. 2 no. 2-6, 8-18, Feb. 24-Dec. 8, 1978; v. 3 no. 1-11, March 16-Sept. 28, 1979; v. 4 no. 1, April 1980, 22.
  - Socialist Labour League Central Committee Newsletter (London, England), no. 667-687, July 1-Sept. 23, 1969, 23.
  - Socialist Revolution (San Francisco, CA), v. 1 no. 1-5, Jan.-Oct. 1970, 24.
  - Socialist Standard (London, England), v. 65 no. 77, May 1969, 25.
  - Socialist Tribune (Los Angeles, CA: Socialist Party), v. 1 no. 5-7, July-Oct. 1969; v. 2 no. 7-10, Jan.-Sept. 1970; v. 3 no. 1-9, Jan.-Dec. 1971; v. 4 no. 1-3, Jan.-Summer 1971; v. 5 no. 2-4, June-Sept./Oct. 1973, 26.
  - Socialist Worker for Workers Control and International Socialism (London, England), no. 122, 129-163, 165-172, May 15, July 3, 1969-March 19, 1970, April-May 23, 1970, 27.
  - Society for Social Responsibility in Science Newsletter (Gambier, OH), no. 95-96, July-Aug. 1960, 28.
  - Science and Society (New York, NY), v. 13 no. 3-4, Summer-Fall 1949; v. 17 no. 3-4, Summer-Fall 1953; v. 18-28 no. 2, 1954-Spring 1964, 1. (Box 114)
  - Solidarity (New York, NY: Labor Committee of New York Students for a Democratic Society), v. 1, no. 1-5, 9-10, 1968; v. 2 no. 1, 4, 1969; v. 6 no. 3, undated, 1. (Box 115)
  - Solidarity for Worker's Control (London, England: Solidarity South London), no. 1-8, March-Dec. 1969, 2.
  - Solidarity for Workers' Power (London, England), v. 3 no. 5-12, Aug. 1964-Aug. 1965; v. 4 no. 2-12, July 1966-Feb. 1968; v. 5 no. 6-12, Dec. 1968-July 1969, 3.
  - Soul Force (Atlanta, GA: Southern Christian Leadership Conference), v. 1 no. 4, June 19, 1968; v. 2 no. 2, June 1969, 4.
  - Soulbook (Berkeley, CA), v. 2 no. 4, Spring/Summer 1969; v. 3 no. 1, Fall/Winter 1970, 5.
  - Southern Africa (New York, NY: Southern Africa Committee), v. 5 no. 10, Dec. 1972; v. 6 no. 1-2, 4-6, 8-10, Jan.-Dec. 1973; v. 7 no. 1-4, 6-11, Jan.-Dec. 1974; v. 8 no. 1-11, Jan.-Dec. 1975; v. 9 no. 1-2, 4-5, 7-11, Jan.-Dec. 1976; v. 10 no. 1-6, Jan.-July 1977, 6.
  - Southern Courier (Montgomery, AL), v. 4 no. 25-49, June-Dec. 1968, 7.
  - Southern Patriot (Louisville, KY: Southern Conference Educational Fund), v. 25 no. 5-6, May-June 1967; v. 26 no. 7-10, Sept.-Dec. 1968; v. 27-34, 1969-1976, 8.
  - Southern Struggle (Louisville, KY: Southern Conference Educational Fund), v. 35-36 no. 2, 1977-Feb. 1978, 9.
  - Spark (San Francisco, CA), July-Aug., Oct., Dec. 1967; no. 19, Feb. 1973, 1. (Box 116)
  - Spartacist (New York, NY), no. 1-20, Feb. 1964-May 1, 1971, 2.
  - Speak Out (Detroit, MI: Facing Reality Publishing Committee), v. 1 no. 1-22, Nov. 1966-July 1968; v. 2, no. 1-6, Jan. 1969-June 1969, 3.
  - Spring Movement (Washington, DC), Spring 1971, 4.
  - Stalinist Workers Group Bulletin (New York, NY: Stalinist Workers Group for Afro-American National Liberation and a New Communist International), no. 1-10, May 1970-Dec. 1971, 5.
  - Student Action (San Bernadino, CA: Campus Crusade for Christ), 1 issue, undated, 6.
  - Student Mobilizer (New York, NY), v. 1 no. 3-5, July-Sept. 1967, 7.
  - Student Voice (Atlanta, GA), v. 5 no. 6, Feb. 18, 1964, 8.
  - Studies on Chinese Communism (Taipei, Taiwan: Institute for the Study of Chinese Communist Problems), v. 1 no. 3, March 31, 1967, 9.
  - Studies on the Left (New York, NY), v. 1-3 no. 1, 1960-1962, 10.
  - Sun Reporter (San Francisco, CA), v. 26 no. 29-32, 37-52, 1969, 11.
  - Texas Observer (Austin, TX), v. 60 no. 5-25, March 15-Dec. 27, 1968; v. 61, 1969; v. 62 no. 1-10, Jan. 2-May 15, 1970; v. 65 no. 21, Nov. 2, 1973, 12.
  - Tell It Like It Is Newsletter: "Voice of a Valley Ghetto Mexican", 1 issue, undated, 13.
  - 34 Street (Philadelphia, PA), v. 1 no. 1-2, Oct. 11-Oct. 25, 1968, 14.
  - This Is the Black World (Pacoima, CA), v. 1 no. 2, 4, Nov. 1970, Feb. 1971, 15.
  - Thunder (Georgetown, Guyana), v. 19 no. 2, Feb. 1968, 16.
  - Thrust (Pittsburgh, PA), v. 1 no. 3, July 27, 1968, 17.
  - Tin Tu'o'ng (Paris, France), March 1970, 18.
  - Together (Palo Alto, CA), v. 2 no. 1, Winter 1970, 19.
  - Trans-Action (St. Louis, MO), v. 6, no. 5-8, March-June, 1969, 20
  - Transformation (Toronto, Ont.), v. 1 no. 1-2, Jan./Feb.-March/April 1971; v. 2 no. 4, Summer 1972, 21.
  - Treason (New York, NY), Summer 1967; Winter 1968, 22.
  - Tribune: Labour's Independent Weekly (London, England), v. 33 no. 20, May 16, 1969, 23.
  - Tri-Continental Information Center Bulletin (New York, NY), v. 1 no. 1-8, May 1967-Dec. 1967; v. 2 no. 1-5, Jan.-May 1968, 24.